Welcome to the future of retail learning. Welcome to RetailEdge Pro, presented by Idonneous.
Frontline performance drives retail success. RetailEdge Pro empowers your promoters
with standard learning paths, rich training videos, and interactive course players.
Evaluate frontline readiness instantly with our robust Assessment Engine,
or transform standard testing into a gamified race with the Live Quiz Arena—
featuring real-time multi-user lobbies, interactive scoreboards, and instant leaderboards.
Empower your operations team with role-based dashboards.
Managing Directors track training ROI. COOs monitor campaign execution and checklist compliance.
VP of Operations audit regional zones, while Program Managers and Supervisors handle user rosters.
Our responsive mobile application keeps promoters connected anywhere,
supporting offline quizzes that auto-sync to prevent data loss.
Upon success, verified certificates are issued instantly to confirm workforce readiness.
Leverage predictive AI insights to flag compliance gaps and receive automated training recommendations.
Boost onboarding speed by forty-five percent, hit ninety-four percent compliance, and elevate store productivity.
RetailEdge Pro: Build Capability. Drive Performance. Transform Outcomes.
Speak with our team at the booth to start your journey.