Idonneous proudly presents RetailEdge Pro, a next-generation learning
and workforce development ecosystem built specifically for retail and FMCG operations.
Traditional frontline training is inconsistent and difficult to track.
RetailEdge Pro solves this by unifying course libraries, interactive assessments,
automated certifications, and real-time dashboards into a single, secure environment.
Role-based access provides tailored experiences.
Executives like the Managing Director, COO, and VP of Operations gain immediate visibility
into national compliance, store launch readiness, and ROI.
Meanwhile, Program Managers and Supervisors assign courses, track attendance, and coach teams.
Frontline promoters access structured learning paths on responsive mobile devices,
joining live gamified quiz arenas and downloading cached materials for offline use.
When training is complete, the platform issues verified certificates automatically.
Driven by predictive AI analytics, the system flags at-risk learners
and suggests custom training topics before compliance gaps impact sales.
Organizations deploying RetailEdge Pro report a forty-five percent reduction in onboarding time,
ninety-four percent compliance levels, and an eighteen percent increase in retail sales.
RetailEdge Pro is more than a learning management system.
It is a complete workforce enablement platform designed to build capability
and drive business results.
Empower your learning. Drive your performance.
Partner with Idonneous today.